COOKIE MONSTER: Now, what starts
with the letter C?
Cookie starts with C. Let's
think of other things that
starts with C. Ah, who cares
about other things?
C is for cookie.
That's good enough for me.
Oh, cookie, cookie, cookie
starts with C.
Oh, C is for cookie.
That's good enough for me.
C is for cookie.
Oh, cookie, cookie, cookie
starts with C.
Hey, you know what?
A round cookie with one bite
out of it looks like a C. A
round donut with one bite out of
it also looks like a C. But
it is not as good as a cookie.
The moon sometimes looks like
a C. But you can't eat that.
So C is for cookie.
That's good enough for me.
Yeah.
C is for cookie.
That's good enough for me.
Oh, cookie, cookie, cookie
starts with C. Yeah.
Cookie, cookie, cookie starts
with C. Oh, boy.
Cookie, cookie, cookie
starts with C.
[COOKIE MONSTER MUNCHING].